NO ANIMALS WERE HARMED DURING THE
FILMING OF THIS PRODUCTION
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com
Most of the soldiers Osman killed…
… are torn into pieces by wild animals.
What about these ones?
For the ceremony, we brought the ones
who were still one piece.
All of them gave their lives for my son.
They are now my children who will live
till the infinity and beyond.
We are looking for their murderers,
Geyhatu.
Their souls will be honored.
We will save Möngke.
Osman!
Blood!
Erlik Khan…
… they got killed for my son.
Honor their souls!
Wipe out and curse all those murderers!
Oh, Erlik Khan!
Your black mount!
Your black rein!
Your whip, a black snake!
You are the mightiest of all!
Oh, Erlik Khan!
Take the souls of my soldiers.
Give me my son, oh Erlik Khan!
Wait for me, Kayı.
I’m coming to terrorize you all!
My Bey, I understand you want to come to
terms with Nikola.
However…
…don’t you think these conditions are too
harsh for both sides?
An eye for an eyes is Fardh for the
sons of Abraham, Dündar
Whether a christian or a jew..
… none can reject.
Also, those terms related to concessions
about trading…
… and the safety of merchants...
... will drive him into a corner.
None can question your words, my Bey.
You know better than me.
As long as you feed a snake in its pit...
… it won’t try to bite you.
Till we are completely done with the
terrors of Geyhatu…
… you will keep Nikola busy with this
agreement.
It’s your duty as the ambassador.
Do you understand?
We will do what's necessary once this
trouble ends.
As long as we have Allah with us.
Has Gündüz left for Kulacahisar?
He left after the morning prayer, my Bey.
Spit it out, Dündar.
My Bey…
… why are you keeping my Osman away
from this?
That path is harsh and long…
… sometimes one will have to stop and
get rest…
… so that he will get his strength and
mind back.
May you live long, My Bey.
May Allah never take you from us.
Apprentice, where have you been?
I haven’t seen you in the workshop.
Let him be free today, Davut Usta.
A day is nothing.
Only for your sake, my Osman Bey.
Come on then!
Let the people see some real archery!
Swing it!
Swing!
The arrow has left the bow.
May it be for good.
Since when these elegant eyes started to
fill with sorrow…
… while I’m off duty, Hatun?
I saw you fighting with hundreds of
enemies and my eyes didn’t even move once.
This duty of yours isn’t fighting, my Bey.
Your destination is the Devil’s pit.
My father gave me a very important
duty, Hatun.
Not only the people in our Tent but also
the people in other Tents...
… ,as well as all the Anatolian
Greeks, have held their breath…
… waiting for the message, I’m going to
bring.
This is what I fear, my Savcı.
Your father gave you the mission to
stop a whole army by yourself.
Why do those tyrants are coming at us?
Geyhatu thinks that Osman has
captured, his son, Möngke.
Because of this, he wants to attack us.
Which snake’s pit, Osman Bey stuck his
stick this time?
My brother, Osman, is being accused
for no reason.
You are the one who is solving the problem
he brought upon us.
Those men are tyrants.
What if they try to kill you?
I will be doomed.
And miserable, my Savcı.
If he is the grandson of Genghis Khan…
… I’m the son of Ertugrul, Hatun.
My father has handed me the safety of
these lands.
Your duty is not the think of my life
and safety but my victory.
Do you understand?
Our future is in your hands.
I’m proud of you.
Allah is eternal!
Allah is the truth!
-Allah is the truth!
-Allah is eternal!
The fire is calling for you, my Bey.
Do you hear it?
It would be ashamed of itself, if it
knew about the fire in me.
Sorrow will be gone, only when it’s
shared.
And the flame gets stronger when
more fuel added.
I’m waiting for the time it dies down.
-May Allah be with you, my Bey.
-Thank you.
Don’t let this flag end up on the floor
even if Geyhatu takes your head.
Oguz’s head may drop on the floor…
… but his honor always stands
straight just like the minaret.
Don't you worry.
We will fight but Allah is the one who
makes us victorious.
Our Tent’s future is in your hands, son.
You must find a way to stop Geyhatu.
Don’t you forget about this.
I will never do that, Bey Father.
With Allah’s permission, I will get rid
of this trouble.
May Allah protect you.
May you live long, my Bey.
We will be waiting for your good news.
May you live long, uncle.
Brother…
… your duty is tough.
You will enter the pit of snakes.
May Allah help you.
May you live long, brother.
Once I’m here, we will train together.
Horses are ready, my Bey.
Did anybody see you?
No, my Bey.
Then, may Allah help us.
My Bey, what if Ertugrul Bey understands?
Our life and our swords belong to no one
but Ertugrul Bey.
But, if stop following Osman Bey’s
path, our cause will be in danger.
Let’s go.
Osman!
I know what you are about to do.
So, you know I won’t stop.
Who’s telling you to stop?
It is time.
It seems that Ertuğrul Bey is
quite displeased with me.
Since he sent you instead.
What you’re doing is dangerous, Nikola.
I’ve come to your
castle to visit and then…
… discuss the agreement.
Could the fact that Geyhatu’s armies
are marching towards you…
… be the reason why
Ertuğrul Bey sent you instead?
Dündar Bey?
Dündar Bey…
If you think I’m unaware of
all the things happening…
… that means you’re greatly mistaken.
What gives, my Osman?
Did you get lost in the forest?
Osman…
Where are you Alps?
Are you out hunting by yourself?
I couldn’t let my brother
hunt infidels alone.
So, I also came.
Were you afraid of losing your pray?
When did my brother
ever let an infidel run away?
You’ll go back to the tent, Osman.
Brother. Let me come with you.
If my father wanted you to come…
… he would have given you duty as well.
Right, brother?
Allow me to come to
Geyhatu’s Tent with you.
What the man wants is to kill you.
Brother! I’m afraid something
will happen to you because of me!
What if something happens to you?
What will I tell my father then, Osman?
Answer, brother!
What will I tell him?
Did you ever think about this?
You’re done for if my father finds
out that you did this.
I’ve been fighting the Mongols
since last year, brother.
I know what they think and how they feel.
Geyhatu will learn the truth
if he listens to me.
I’m coming with you.
Osman!
Enough! Go back to the Tent.
I will not!
I wonder. While we’re fighting a plague,
you’ve come to the Tent and raised hell.
You’ve shed the blood of our Alps.
Is this the way you see peace?
Is this the friendship you’re offering?
Didn’t Savcı Bey enter my lands
and steal my ammunition?
Didn’t he kill my soldiers?
Dündar Bey…
If someone’s going to
call someone account for…
… that’s me.
What are you even doing with
the Mongol’s flying fire?
I like to take precautions.
Yes, precautions.
What precautions? Governor Nikola?
You expected us to go for your lands
while we’re dealing with Mongols?
You’re trying to take the revenge of
the past with Mongols as an excuse.
Tell me. What are you up to?
Kulacahisar or Söğüt?
I just want peace.
But remember, Dündar Bey. Osman came and
took Kulacahisar in your most desperate times.
Why and how should I trust you?
Shouldn’t I take any precautions?
Trust is mutual, Nikola.
If you still want peace,
you will obey the rules.
Then there’s only one rule.
An eye for an eye.
Be frank!
As it’s written on your
holy book, Dündar Bey.
Believers! Retribution is prescribed
for you in cases of killing.
If a freeman is guilty then the freeman.
If a slave is guilty then the slave.
If a female is guilty, then the female.
Looks like you did your homework, Nikola.
As it’s written in your book.
Treat people the way you
want to be treated.
Correct?
Correct.
Then, if you plant seeds of
evil to the garden of peace…
… you harvest evil.
If you plant seeds of evil…
… you pay the price for it.
Is this also valid for Ertuğrul Bey?
Everyone pays for what they
did during peaceful times.
No one should make promises
they won’t be able to keep, Nikola.
Ertuğrul Bey wrote and stated the article
you’re so excited about beforehand.
And we say…
… an eye for an eye.
An eye for an eye.
Alps!
Contain Osman Bey!
Don’t, brother!
I’m talking to you, Alps! Now!
My Allah, don’t make me do this!
Brother!
Don’t!
He doesn’t listen to his Bey!
He doesn’t listen to his father!
He doesn’t listen to his brother.
What have you become, Osman?
Alps!
Don’t Savcı Bey, don’t!
I know that I can trust your word as much
as I trust my Emperor’ss word, Dündar Bey.
We’ll see that together, Nikola.
Alps! Take him.
Don’t make me do these, brother!
Geyhatu wants me, not you!
I killed both Balgay and Subutay!
If there’s someone to settle accounts
with, that’s me! Not you!
Oh, Osman! Oh, my brother!
You’re blind!
My father is trying to protect you,
don’t you see?
Is it your job to protect me, brother?
It is, yes!
It is our job!
Do you know why?
They have kidnapped Möngke!
Geyhatu is sure that you did it!
That’s why he’s marching
at us with his army!
It’s because of you, brother!
You!
It’s you.
Someone’s using you for
their tricks, brother.
The trap in our Tent
is bigger than you think.
There are traps within traps, brother!
That’s why I’m coming.
I will face Geyhatu so that he can see
that I have nothing to do with it.
I will come with you
whether you like it or not.
Nothing can take me to the Tent!
Osman!
Father?
Since when you don’t listen to
the word of you Bey, Osman?
What do you mean, father?
I’d rather get stumbled on by horses
rather than disobey the word of my Bey.
Then what are you doing here?
I’m here to protect my brother from
the wrath of Geyhatu, father.
If you allow me, I want to go with him.
Take your Alps and go back to the Tent.
If I don’t see you when I’m at the Tent,
I don’t want to see you ever again.
-Father--
- Osman do as I say!
Osman is unpredictable, father. What
should I do if he comes after me again?
The punishment of disobeying
my order is certain.
I can make no excuses.
You will give him the harshest
punishment if he comes again.
As you order, my Bey.
If you’ll excuse me…
Let your mind be bright, your path clear,
your sword sharp, son.
Mashallah!
You’ve done plenty! Lena Hatun,
they always said you were hard working.
But we didn’t expect this much!
I didn’t do anything.
Bala is a very nimble Hatun.
She could make supplies for
not just the Kayı…
… but every surrounding Tents for winter.
That’s true, I know.
Bala Hatun is our Tent’s arms and hands.
And Osman Bey is its eyes and ears.
You know where Osman went, Bala.
If Savcı finds out that Osman went
after him, it wouldn’t be good.
How do you know that Lena?
I know Osman as well as
I know Savcı, Bala.
He is his brother after all. Of course
you know him.
When it comes to his duty, Savcı doesn’t
care if someone’s his brother or not.
What are you talking about Lena?
Hatuns! If siblings fight
each other, we’re done for. Know that.
The Tent went through a lot because
of those who were acting on their own.
Bala!
You should get a hold of Osman.
Look. Savcı Bey isn’t
like Dündar or Gündüz.
I see that you’re the
one fanning the flame, Hazal Hatun.
Never!
If you want the put out
the fire of unrest, water it.
Can’t believe what I’m hearing.
Osman.
Our love suppresses
the mountain-shaking anger of yours.
You have become
the solution to my problems.
- I know it’s hard. - I know it’s harsh.
Your breath is out of
order, my dear friend.
What caused this anger?
Falling into the trap of Ertuğrul!
What does that mean?
The agreement that you sealed!
This will trap us! You are
making a mistake Nikola!
That goatherd trapped you!
Goatherd? The "goatherd"
that killed your father?
Don't you talk about my
father like that again, never.
We came here for our children's future,
Vladius, not for our fathers' revenge.
Until I take my father's revenge,
I don't care about children's future.
I like your restless spirit.
But remember, Vladius, the great
warriors that passed through seas...
... change the skies, not their souls.
We'll show the rains of holy Byzantine to
the Turks that turned Söğüt into a swamp.
And we will do all these with the
help of the agreement that I sealed.
-Salaimun Alaikum
-Alaikum Salam, Bey son.
May it be easy.
Easier said than done.
You are just sharpening
a knife, Kumral Abdal.
Sharpening a knife is for everyone. Being
Ismail and making a knife is for the wise.
Being Ismail is easy to say, hard to do.
I heard, it's truth.
Boran came here with haste.
I said " Which scorpion's nest
did Bey's son disturb again?"
Geyhatu.
Geyhatu? Wow...
All this rush for that weakling?
Miserable people like us
have weak enemies like those.
It's okay, there is always a solution.
I am listening, Bey's son.
There is a game inside
another game. A big one.
My brother went to Geyhatu.
Maybe his dead body
will come out of there.
If all this rush is for saving your
brother, don't you bother me, Bey's son.
If the fate is written,
no one can stand in its way.
He wants me. They blame
me for Möngke's abduction.
If we don't do something,
many innocent people will be hurt.
What do you want from me?
To be my remedy.
Now you are talking my
language, Bey's son. I am listening.
You know Normans the best.
You can tell me where their base is.
We are ready with my Alps.
I will prepare the game this time.
Blood! Blood! Blood!
They are messengers!
Get back, you idiots!
Who are you?
Savcı Bey, son of Ertuğrul Ghazi!
I came here as a messenger.
Kill them.
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim.
Osman isn't here yet?
Osman rode somewhere, my Bey.
He will be here soon.
Where is Osman, daughter?
Can't you speak, daughter?
Didn't he tell you where he was going?
I wonder too, my Bey.
As-Sirāt is thinner than a hair,
sharper than a sword.
We don't only pass from
this bridge in afterlife.
Sometimes, we need to
pass them in this life too.
Those who pass them are called heroes.
Then, what is the secret of
those who pass them, father?
If one stays strong in the face
of disasters, control one's anger...
... keep one's heart clean, one can
pass through As-Sirāt in this life too.
Fortunately, my Savcı
has all those traits.
Savcı Bey rose on our Tent like a sun.
Long may he live. Osman Bey...
... wouldn't leave
without a word, my Bala.
Is there something that troubles him?
The only thing that troubles
Osman Bey is the future of his Tent...
Hazal Hatun, don't you know?
Can I come in, my Bey?
Come, son.
I am sorry.
If I am allowed, I would want to sit.
Tell us, Dündar, what else did
you talk about with Nikola?
I know where Möngke, your son is!
Stop!
Bring him...
... to my tent.
Leave.
Nikola already knew that
Geyhatu was coming, my Bey.
He has spies everywhere.
He signed the agreement anyway?
He said " While Geyhatu is coming,
we wouldn't backstab you...
... be sure of it.
So I sign this agreement."
My Dündar Bey went to that
infidel just in time, my Bey.
At least we have our back safe.
Don't be so sure about it, aunt.
Emperor gave Nikola the
mission to retake those lands.
What about it?
He killed Inegöl's Lord
the moment he came.
He could've used the equipments
he tried to bring here...
... to take Kulucahisar,
Karacahisar and then Söğüt.
When we are weakest.
No one suspects that, Osman.
We will always be watchful.
This is not enough, uncle.
What should we do then, nephew?
We should've striked Nikola harder...
... while he was trapped on a corner.
While Geyhatu is coming to us?
Speak, Osman, what are you thinking?
They will use this "An eye for an eye"
agreement as a weapon.
Sooner or later.
Aren't you Beys?
You will keep your eyes open, so that...
... he wouldn't hit you
in your weak spot...
... he wouldn't punish you
for your sweet dreams.
That's enough.
Lena, bring more of your delicious food.
I will, father.
Where is my son, Möngke?
You will learn when I bring him to you.
You are lying!
If you don't tell his place,
at least tell us who did it.
Or you will get out of this
tent impaled on a stake.
If your dog stays silent,
I have words for you, Geyhatu.
Those who abducted your son,
are the ones who are waiting to end you.
Know that.
He is just like Osman.
Tells 40 lies on foot, 80 on the ground.
Shut up!
Who are those that want to end me?
The ones who know they
can't deal with you in Konya...
... and wants to waste you and
your army away from Konya.
What does that mean? Spit
that poison you hid behind your teeth!
Speak!
You should learn the truth from the ones
who blamed this on my brother, Geyhatu.
I know very well that my brother is
innocent, and where your son is.
But, I will prove that
when I bring him to you.
Give me 3 days.
How do you know that my son is not dead?
I know my brother, Osman.
If he had captured your son
when he attacked your Tent...
... he would've already ripped
his heart, and sent his head to you.
Just like he sent Subutay's head to you.
But, I am grateful that...
... my brother doesn't have your son.
I know he is alive,
and the place they keep him.
Give me 3 days, Geyhatu, only 3 days.
I will bring your son to you.
Do you know what will
happen if you are lying?
I know what will happen to Kayıs,
but you don't know...
... what will happen to you, Geyhatu.
You will be at war with
my father, far from Konya.
In this war, neither my father give Osman
to you, nor you can have your son, Möngke.
Both sides will fight
until the last drop of blood.
Just like you trying to save your son,
I want to save my Tent from your wrath.
But, if something happens
to me or to my Tent...
... then first your son,
then you will pay for it.
Why me?
Because they are not interested in your
son. It's about Ilkhanate's throne!
This is not our war, Geyhatu.
This is Mongols' fight for dynasty!
They want you to fight
us by blaming Osman.
Keep your eyes open, Geyhatu.
These are my words.
This Kayı wants to fool you, Geyhatu.
Shut up!
Know what I'll do, Turk!
I will go to Söğüt with my army...
... to kill all your family,
and to take my son back!
I give you three days!
Three days! Three days!
Then, I will be in Söğüt with my army.
Either you will bring me my son back...
... or...
Listen to me carefully.
Ya Allah!
With the name of Allah!
A secret doesn't get revealed.
A secret makes love with the
roots of the trees...
...seven feet underground.
It makes love but...
...it doesn't get revealed.
A dream of building a state isn't easy...
...it isn't easy.
Wen the need shows up, the truth reveals
itself like the sun...
...then the secrets get revealed too.
I, Bamsı Beyrek...
...mountains, steppes were too
little for me...
...but I lived underground for
too long.
Now, there is a need...
...now, it's time to make
the dream true.
My holy valiant, my faithful friend...
...Ertuğrul Bey...
...now is the time to realize a dream.
Ya Allah!
Take care of yourself.
Get well soon.
Be careful for a little
while longer.
Lena, these were the last of the
medicines.
We got rid of the plague, Gonca.
We can make new ones if needed.
With Dündar Bey's efforts and your
experience, we are good now.
Keep it in your mouth for a while. Don't
swallow it. It will give you strength.
Rest at home for a while.
Bala is a solid person, too. It's a good thing
that she shared her knowledge with you.
Many lives were saved with the medicines
you made.
-May Allah bless you both.
-Thank you.
You did a lot, as well, Gonca Hatun.
Look how you wish for good.
Remember, the best medicine is love.
Gonca Hatun, I will check the horses
and come back.
Start the preparations.
I'll be back in a moment.
What do you want?
Trails end here.
Give an order, my bey.
You didn't change your name
or your religion.
I didn't forget who I am,
I won't.
It's not too late.
I have a son at the same height as you.
Everyone makes mistakes.
I still love you, Lena.
Dying at your hands?
It'd be nice.
My soldiers...
If you don't want to die by the hands
of my first and only love...
...don't face me again...
...you hound.
Sooner or later, Lena.
Where is Möngke?
You didn't know where he is...
...you played us and Geyhatu.
-Who are you and where is Möngke?
-ı wouldn't tell you even if I knew.
Where is Möngke?
-Where is Möngke?
-All right, enough! I will tell you!
I'll tell you.
I swear I don't know where he is.
Just in Blacksea, at a dead harbor.
They are hiding him underground,
in a cellar.
Yes.
This pot is full, Ahmed.
Put it on the fire.
What happened to you?
Tell me, Ahmed.
Why is Ertuğrul bey treating Osman Bey
like that?
What kind of words is those, Ahmed?
Ertuğrul Bey's sons are his pieces.
Why would he trreat Osman Bey badly?
Wasn't it Osman Bey who saved our
tents from the Mongols?
Isn't he the one who conquered
Kulucahisar?
Come on, let's put the pot on the fire.
-Osman Bey
-Ahmed Alp.
Ahmed, put this pot on the fire.
Even this little child knows.
But my father doesn't.
You can talk to your father tonight,
Osman.
Ertuğrul Bey is your father.
He will listen to you.
Just try to talk to him.
My bey! My bey!
Help me, they'll kill my father!
-Where is he, show me!
-This way, my bey.
Have you had enough fun?
Get up, brother!
-Thank you, Turk!
-You want some, Turk?
Don't meddle.
Put that dagger down.
There will be no blood.
Die, Turk!
Enough, enough, enough!
Enough!
-What's happening here, Göktuğ?
-These three were beating the Rum.
-I intervened.
-We had a bet.
We had no problem before this
Turk showing up.
It's true, my bey.
I didn't understand it, either.
This alp attacked unarmed guards
with his dagger.
-Lying dog! Lying dog!
-Göktuğ!
-He is losing too much blood.
-Take him to the public house.
Call the physicians.
Dündar Bey, these dogs are lying!
While your lord is signing a peace
deal with Lord Nicola...
...you are stabbing us from the
back here, Dündar Bey.
I'll find out what happened, Vladius.
I will.
You attacked my armless soldiers.
La Hawla.
(Wishing patience)
You must avoid imputating which you
are going to regret later, Vladius.
Ertuğrul Bey should pay for my soldier's
life.
Tit-for-tat, Dündar Bey.
- You liar!
- Göktüğ!
Göktuğ!
I am not like an armless soldier,
you Mongol offspring!
Göktuğ!
- I will cut your tongue!
- Göktuğ!
- I'll kill you!
- Calm down! calm down!
Calm down!
Take him to dungeon.
Take his swords away.
Ertuğrul Bey will decide what will happen.
If something happens to my soldier,
you'll pay for it.
Dündar Bey.
Do you know the story of the cat with
stomped tail?
What happened to the cat?
She lost her food.
What are you talking about?
-Tell me what happened.
-Osman Bey's coming, don't you understand?
He shall come. We have cold
ayran(a beverage) and a good talk.
I'm saying that things will get crazy,
and you're talkin about ayran? I'm leaving
Wait.
- Tell me what it is.
- Ertuğrul Bey has news from Söğütlü.
When Osman Bey hears about it, he'll
go mad, Master Davut.
Here he is.
What are we going to say?
We know what we have to do.
Tell it to Osman Bey then.
In a proper way!
- Salam Alaikum.
- Alaikum Salam.
What happened?
You look pale.
You're out of breath.
Tell me.
Göktuğ Bey injured Nikola's
unarmed soldier in Söğüt.
Soldier is losing blood. Dündar Bey sent
him to dungeon. They want tit for tat.
If the soldier dies, they say Göktuğ
will be executed, my Bey.
What have you done, İdris?
You told it all in once!
May Allah grant us with the good.
Can I come in, my Bey?
Come in, son.
I know you are young and excited.
I understand that.
I don't want to be rebel, my father.
We all knew Nikola would do something
villainy.
What is going to happen now father?
I warned you to be careful!
You couldn't take care of your Alp Göktuğ.
You put me in a difficult situation, Osman.
Göktuğ is in dungeon.
What is going to happen now father?
Are you going to let my Alp die
because of the rule tit for that?
Don't you know that I am going to do what
I have to do if he is guilty, Osman?
Father, how can you say this?
Aren't you Ertuğrul Bey?
We offered this agreement. They accepted.
And you men ruined everything in
the first day!
Osman, who can't take care of his Alps!
I conquered castles with my Alps.
I defeated the enemy when you
were not here.
They didn't go behind my back like my
uncle or my brother.
Get over it, Osman!
While bothering with Beyhatu, you opened
a new war.
Your Alps ruined the game I had been
planning.
Father.
Father...
Are you really Ertuğrul Bey?
His very self!
Do not ever interfere in this issue.
Or, it will cost you dearly.
What have I done, father?
What have I done to fall from
your grace?
In Beyship position, there's
no son and father. You should know that.
Our first objective is our tribe's peace.
Son is the secret of father.
Ararya Hadrat was right to state this
sentence..
I like good news, Vladius.
- Tell it to me with joy!
- Just like what we thought.
Göktuğ ate the bait.
You should have seen Göktuğ and Dündar's
despair, Nikola.
When Ertuğrul learns this, he will be
bad with Osman.
Of course.
What is the condition of
the wounded soldier?
He is not wounded anymore.
What do you mean.
I made the game more covincing.
How did you do it?
I killed him.
Well played.
You drove Osman's Alp crazy
You deserve this.
I am happy to serve you, even though
I'm hurt.
Good job.
Soldier!
Go want justice for our death soldier!
Collect the gold also.
They will find his body.
Send you spies to Söğütlü from now,
Vladius.
Osman will want to save his Alp.
Try not to face him.
If necessary, ambush him.
And never ever never...
do something without my knowledge
and go beyond my orders!
- Is it right, Boran?
- Yes, my Bey.
Göktuğ is in dungeon. His life is dependent
on Ertuğrul Bey an Nikola!
There is something wrong with this!
Absolutely.
- Göktuğ doesn't kill someone armless.
- I know, my Bey.
We will save Göktuğ from dungeon.
Are we going to disobey Ertuğrul Bey?
Nikola wants to put my father in a
difficult position.
We won't let this.
Nikola and Vladius will come to Söğüt,
my Bey.
We need to do it before they come.
Lİsten tomecarefully name.
Be ready!
My Bey, these are dressed like the others.
It's not clear that whose dogs are they.
Pigeons brought us the nest of snakes.
Hold on.
Eyvallah (okay) my Bey.
I am not a killer.
I am not.
Stop!
Who are you?
Alps!
Who are you? Let alps be free!
Come to me!
Come to me! Who are you!
Abdurrahman Ghazi!
My valiant!
Masha Allah(praise be) my valiant.
After Geyhatu issue passes, Osman Bey
will hide you.
Eyvallah (thank you) Abdurrahman Ghazi.
I am here under the order of my Ertuğrul Bey.
Even if there's death in the end, I won't
leave.
My lion, do I ever disobey Ertuğrul Bey?
Is there Ertuğrul Bey behind this?
Come on. without drawing atteniton,
leave Söğüt, find Osman Bey.
Come on.
Eyvallah (thank you) Abdurrahman Ghazi.
Eyvallah (okay) my lion.
Is it true, Leyla?
We were just getting over the plague,
and those came up!
This Göktuğ put my Ertuğrul Bey
in a difficult situation.
Like Osman was not enough!
Our Ertuğrul Bey will surely protect
Göktuğ.
- Don't be sure about that.
- Hazal Hatun is right, Bala.
I don;'t understand.
Göktuğ wouldn't kill an unarmed soldier.
Even if this is true, Ertuğrul Bey has
made an agreement with Nikola.
Be sure that he will remain true to
his word.
It is Osman's battle friend
Göktuğ we are talking about, Hazal Hatun
Put Göktuğ aside, even if it was Osman...
Ertuğrul Bey wouldn't retract
his agreement.
Who are they?
Who are you?!
- I'll take you to Geyhatu.
- Why are you doing this, Turk?
Not for your life.
Fight for your life.
What I heard are true, Dündar Bey?
Yes.
Göktuğ Alp argued with
one of your soldiers.
Then a death happened.
But my soldier died.
In your city.
There will be a response to this.
It wasn't intentional, you
should know that.
What have we talked about?
An eye for an eye.
I like people
who keep their words, Dündar Bey.
Where is Ertuğrul Bey?
He's in his room, waiting for you.
Osman Bey is on his way.
Just as I want.
- Are his Alps (men) with him?
- No, he's alone.
It's time to payoff, Osman.
Let's go.
Can I come in, my Bey?
Come in.
Nikola, Governor of
Yenigöl Castle, is here.
Whenever I make an agreement with you...
I'm hurt, Ertuğrul Bey.
I heard what happened, Governor Nikola.
My condolences.
- May rest in peace.
- Your Alp, who didn't listen to your orders...
killed my young soldier.
Ertuğrul Bey.
My soldiers are angry.
They want the cost.
You know what I mean.
If you don't call out my Alps...
your dignity...
will fall.
I won't let you do this to me again.
Today, if the scaffold isn't ready...
you should know
that you'll fight in...
two fronts, not one.
Can I come in, my Bey?
Come in.
Göktuğ Alp escaped from the dungeon.
What kind of game
are you in, Ertuğrul Bey?
What kind of game is it?
My Bey...
fighting with you...
was an honor, my Bey.
"I bear witness that there is no
deity but Allah..."
"and I bear witness that Muhammad
is the messenger of Allah."
You...
Don't waste your breath, Kayı boy.
Good job, Möngke.
Good job.
Catch him!
I'll kill you, Osman.
I asked a question, Ertuğrul Bey.
Do you want to play a game with me?
Give me the killer of my soldier or...
or I'll take the sword of justice.
One day, Oghuz Khagan went hunting.
He had a deer and tied it to a tree.
You know why?
He wanted to know the monster that
he wanted to hunt.
He came at dawn.
He saw that...
the monster took the deer.
Ertuğrul Bey.
What do you mean?
Drink this sherbet and take a breath.
There is good stuff in the Turk's sagas.
You'll be good.
You can't run away, Osman!
These lands will be your grave!
This time, Oghuz Khagan...
tied himself to that tree.
He waited.
Then the monster came.
Oghuz Khagan hit the monster's head...
and killed him.
He cut its head.
Ertuğrul Bey!
I'm done with these words.
I can't bear them.
I'll raid your rent with my army
if this keeps going like that.
Like Oghuz Khagan's tree...
Söğüt is my only
tree. (the precious thing)
I wait for you there.
Come whenever you want.
Threat?
I don't like threats, Ertuğrul Bey.
An ammunition raid...
then you kill my innocent soldier!
Your sons are
responsible for them!
Ertuğrul Bey.
You can't even look after a killer.
You can't rule neither your Alp...
nor your sons.
Whether you'll give me
the killer of my soldier...
Or you'll pay the price.
Don't you know I keep my words?
When the time comes...
my Alp will be put on trial
in front of everyone.
You'll witness it.
Do you understand me?
By the way...
If something happens to Göktuğ...
you'll see what the payoff is.
He's there.
Osman!
You're trapped, Osman.
Give me the murderer of my soldier! I
want Göktuğ!
I know you abducted him!
Flatyos.
Did your man die from a little bite?
Or from a nightmare?
Tell me.
You're trapped, Osman. Give us Göktuğ!
I made many dogs like you bow down
to me.
Now it's your turn to bow down.
You'll die!
You'll die.
Bamsı Bey.
My Osman.
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com